Ahmed Ali Gawish

Front-End Developer

№ AhmedGawish22@gmail.com

101064880594

≡ 5 Sep 2001 **♀** Kafr Elsheikh - Egypt

https://github.com/ahmedgawish10

https://linkedin.com/Ahmed-Gawish

Summary

I have bachelor's degree in technology information systems from PortSaid University,

Passionate Front-end developer with expertise in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJs, NextJs and Angular. Gained Skills in creating responsive web designs as a trainee in (ITI), gained ability to collaborate effectively within a team. Committed to continually updating skills.

Familiar with backend technologies such as PHP, MySQL, and Laravel.

Education

Bachelor of technology and information systems, PortSaid University **Cumulative Grade: Very Good with Honors**

2019 - 2023

Work Experience

Front-End Developer at Rukn

May, 2024 - Present

Fullstack Web Developer Course at ITI

January, 2024 - May, 2024

develop web pages and build responsive websites using HTML3, CSS3, JS, jQuery, Bootstrap, Angular, PHP, MySQL, Laravel, Nodejs, WordPress

Others: Docker, Git, Linux

Fundamentals Web Development Summer Training at ITI July . 2022 - August . 2022 develop web pages and build responsive websites using HTML3, CSS3, JS, jQuery, Bootstrap.

Technical Skills

Front-End

Tailwind CSS

React[S

TypeScript

• HTML5 • CSS3

Material UI

Redux

Formik & Yup

SASS

JavaScript

NextIS

React-hook-form & Zod

BootStrap5

¡Query

Angular

• Git & GitHub

📥 Back-End

PHP

• My SQL

• Strapi (CMS)

Laravel

NodeIS

Projects

Graduation Project: Arduino Measure Diabetes

- **Grade**: Excellent
- **Description**: A device consisting of a sensor that is inserted into the patient's arm for a period of 14 days, and then converts the near-range signal into a long-range signal to receive it via Bluetooth and connects it to an application to read the blood sugar result.
- Create website and app store for Arduino.
 - Front-End: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap5, JavaScript and React
 - Measure Diabetes Website: Demo

Projects

Next & Strapi

Al-Jewar Travel Agency App: Demo

Technologies: HTML – CSS- Tailwind - JavaScript – Next.js - i18Next

Courses Tech App: Code

Courses Tech Application is a dynamic online learning platform designed to deliver a seamless educational experience. It is built with Next.js for a responsive and interactive frontend, and **Strapi** for a flexible, scalable backend. Key features include **Clerk** for authentication, **Stripe Technologies**: HTML - CSS- Tailwind - JavaScript - Next.js - Strapi - plugins(Cloudnairy)

PHP & MY SQL

Job Portal App: Code

job portal application designed to streamline the hiring process for organizations. This webbased solution facilitates job postings and candidate applications.

Technologies: HTML - CSS - PHP - MY SQL

React

Portfolio: Demo E-commerce: Demo

> e-commerce website for the medical industry, facilitating the sale of a variety of medical healthy products. The application ensures a smooth shopping experience for customers. Technologies: HTML - CSS - JavaScript - React - Redux Toolkit - react slick carousel - REST API

Angular

Portfolio: Demo E-commerce: Demo

> e-commerce application using Angular with user authentication and lazy Loading for optimized performance. The application uses local storage, ensuring a seamless shopping experience.

Technologies: HTML - CSS -Bootstrap -JavaScript - Angular- REST API

IavaScript

E-commerce Website: demo **Company Template: demo**

Personal Skills

- Good organizational, interpersonal and Communication skills
- Time management skills.
- Self-study.
- High flexibility in thinking and operating style.
- Problem solving.

Languages

Arabic mother tongue

English

conversational